trivok.com 2018-08-19

# Privacy policy

###  General Information 

Trivok.com takes appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure the security, integrity and confidentiality of personal data as provided in Law 15/99 on Protection of Personal Data (LOPD).The Personal Data that is collected automatically treated and incorporated into the file www. Trivok.com 

Anytime you.may exercise their right of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition in that LOPD recognized by writing to info@ Trivok.com or any of the procedures established by the applicable rules. 

###  Data Collection 

Trivok, noting the current legislation in this field reported that personal data collected through browsing through its website and registration forms are included in computer files specific to the company to carry out their services . 

By registering as a user, ensures that the information disclosed is true and accurate and that you will update any changes to data on the site.

v has the right to refuse any future use of the site if it has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or if you do not follow the terms and conditions of this User Agreement.

###  Cookies 

Please note that when the user navigates through our site uses a third company, Google, which includes the use of the DoubleClick DART cookie:   
· Google and third-party provider, use cookies to serve ads on your site.  
· The use of the DART cookie allows Google to post ads to users who visit their sites and other Internet sites.   
· Users can disable the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and the privacy policy of the content network.  
To learn more about this service third visit [ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

If you do not want to receive cookies can configure your browser to notify and reject the installation of cookies sent by the portal, without negatively affecting their access to contents.

###  Electronic communications 

By registering as a user, expressly consent to the sending of a newsletter that includes news, most relevant news and information Web Site, and electronic communications relating to their sector and other sectors that may be of interest.

###  Minors 

Users who contracted through the web site recognize www. Trivok.com be adults. Recruitment conducted by minors requires the written permission of their parents, guardians or legal representatives, which will be held responsible for the recruitment done by the children in their care.Will the children who must obtain the necessary consent to proceed with recruitment. 

###  Security 

We are committed to protecting your privacy and it will take steps to ensure that the information we collect is protected against misuse and access, modification and disclosure is prohibited.

YellCup is committed to protecting the privacy of users of its Web site and uses all reasonable efforts to ensure that retained data are protected from unauthorized access.No security system is impenetrable and therefore we can not guarantee the security of our database. 

By using our services you consent to these privacy provisions.
